Alright ok ok ok ok
Alright ok
BABYMONSTER
I got no worries on my mind
난 멈추지 않아
So you can say goodbye
I’ll fulfill my fantasy
And you can watch and see
박수나 쳐보지
눈부셔
They say she looking flawless
I know
타고났지 Like this
She’s unlike unlike anybody
여기저기 다 난리 난리
가나다라마바 싸가지
Gotta gotta go so c’est la vie
I’m dancing in the moonlight
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ay
Can’t stop this feeling tonight
What you waiting for
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
저 하늘 높이
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
Like I’mma live forever
Like I’mma like I’mma
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever
OK you know what it is
I’m that nice 뭘 것 같아 너와 내 차이
Pull up on me pay the price
Put a milli on a rock my type
Never seen it in your life
예뻐 그러니까 바빠
아니 나빠 온 세상 울리는
Bad girl
B (B) A (A) B (B) Y (Y) M (M) O (O) N
Get money
Bout it bout it 발끝까지 까지
리듬 타지 타지 기분 짜릿짜릿
Everybody get down
Roll up on ‘em with the motor running
I’mma give you something
Bet you put the money in the bag
I’m dancing in the moonlight
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ay
Can’t stop this feeling tonight
What you waiting for
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
저 하늘 높이
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
Like I’mma live forever
Like I’mma like I’mma
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever
I can see the bright horizon
세상이란 벽을 넘어서
No nothing can stop me now
We forever forever
Forever ever ever
Ooh ooh
Baby it was all a dream
You thought I was yours
멋대로 착각하지는 마
It’s bitter it’s sweet
저 하늘 높이
I’m spreading my wings
Like I’mma live
Forever
(Forever ever ever)
Forever (We forever forever forever ever ever)
Forever
Like I’m gonna live
Like I’m gonna live forever